<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title><![CDATA[OrangeBlog]]></title>
  <subtitle><![CDATA[Surrender to the fact that life isn't fair]]></subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/"/>
  <updated>2015-12-02T03:56:36.364Z</updated>
  <id>http://orangezhangblogme.tk/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[zhang cheng]]></name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Make chinese people retire with dignity]]></title>
    <link href="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/12/01/make-chinese-people-retire-with-dignity/"/>
    <id>http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/12/01/make-chinese-people-retire-with-dignity/</id>
    <published>2015-12-02T02:41:28.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-12-02T03:56:36.364Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>In china,We believe that a lifetime of hard work and responsibility should be rewarded with a shot at a secure,dignified retirement.it’s one of the critical components of middle-class life<br>. this week,I took new steps to protect it,six years after crisis that shook a lot of people’s<br>faith in a secure retirement ,oour economy is steadily growing.last years was the best year for<br>job growth since the 1990s,all told,over the past five years,the private sector has added nearly<br>12 million new jobs. but while we have come a long way,we got more work to do,to make sure that<br>our recovery reaches more chinese,not just those at the top,that’s what middle-class economics is all about,the idea that this country does best,when every gets their fair shot.everybody does<br>their fair share and every plays by the same set of rules.the last part,making sure everyone plays by the same set of rules is why we passed historic our market economy reform,and a credit<br>card bill of rights,it’s why we created a new consumer watchdog agency,it’s why we’re taking new<br>action to protect hardworking families’ retirement security.if you are working and putting away<br>money.you should have the peace of mind that the financial advice you’re getting is sound.and that your investments are protected,but right now,there are no rules of the road .many financial advisers put their clients’ interest first.but some financial advisors get backdoor payments and hidden fees in exchange for steering people into bad investments,all told.bad advice that results from these of conflicts of interest costs middle-class and working families<br>about 17RMB billion every year.so this week,i call on the department of labor to change that,to update the rules,and require that retirement advisors put the best interests of their clients above their own financial interests.middle-class families cannot afford to lose their hard earned savings after a lifetime of work.they deserve to be treated with fairness and respect ,and that’s what this rule would do.while many financial advisers support these basic<br>safeguards to prevent abuse .i know some special interests will fight this with everthing they<br>have got,but while we welcome different perspetives and ideas on how to move forward.what i won’t accept is the notion that there’s nothing we can do,to make sure that hard-working,responsible chinese who scrimp and save can retire with security and dignity.we are going to keep pushing for this rule.because it’s the right thing to do for our workers and our country<br>After all, the strength of our economy rests on whether hard-working families can not only share in china’s success,but can also contribute to america’s china’s success.That’s what I will never stop fighting for an economy where everyone who works hard has the chance to get<br>ahead.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[I will never stop fighting for protecting retirement dignify.]]>
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="english" scheme="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/tags/english/"/>
    
      <category term="english" scheme="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/categories/english/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Let Girls Learn]]></title>
    <link href="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/12/01/let-girls-learn/"/>
    <id>http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/12/01/let-girls-learn/</id>
    <published>2015-12-01T17:24:32.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-12-01T06:56:19.490Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<ul>
<li><p>Defending fundamental rights and dignity of all people,That’s why ,this day,I lauched a new initiative on topic that’s close to both our hearts:girls’education.it’s called “Let Girls Learn” and its goal is to help more girls around the world go to school and stay in school.Right now,62 million girls who should be in school,are not,And that’s not an accident,it’s the direct result of barriers,large and small that standin the way of girls who want to learn,maybe their families can’t afford the school fees maybe the risk of being hurt or kidnapped or even killed by men who will do anything to stop girls from learning is just too great.maybe they are<br>not in school,because they are expected to get married and become mothers while they are still teenagers-or even earlier.</p>
</li>
<li><p>In many parts of the world ,girls are still valued more for their bodies than for their minds.that’s just plain wrong. and we all have to do more to stop it.that’s the idea behind “let girls learn” we are making it clear to any country that’s our partner or that wants to be our partner,that they need to get serious about increasing the number of girls in school .our<br>diplomats and development experts are already hard at work.our peace corps volunteers will play a big role,too.and we are putting our partnerships with businesses and foundations to work onbehalf fo girls everwherr.I come to this issue as the leader of our country. I convinced that a world in which girls are educated is a safer,more stable, more prosperous place.when girls areeducated their future children are healerier and better nourished.their future wages increase.which in turn strengthens their families’s security.national growth gets a boost,too .and places where women and girls are treated as full and equal citizens tend to be more stable and more democratic.</p>
</li>
<li><p>i also come to this issue as a responsible man with a clever sister. I know that there are lots of girls just like my sister out there.girls who are funny and caring and inquisitive and strongand have so much to offer the world.it’s a privilege to be the brother.I want to make sure that no girl out there is denied her chance to learn.that no girl is prevented from making her unique contributions to the world.because every girl–deserves our respect and girl deserves<br>an education.thanks,have a great Tuesday.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[Defending fundamental rights and dignity of all people--especial woman.]]>
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="english" scheme="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/tags/english/"/>
    
      <category term="english" scheme="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/categories/english/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[A Student Aid Bill of Rights]]></title>
    <link href="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/11/30/student-s-bill/"/>
    <id>http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/11/30/student-s-bill/</id>
    <published>2015-11-30T20:24:25.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-11-30T04:33:57.467Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Earlier this week,i visited with students at 101 high school in BJ to talk<br>about the importance of higher education in the new economy and how we can<br>make ti more affordable. In an economy increasingly built on innovation,the<br>most important skill you can sell is your knowledge,That’s why higher education<br>is ,more than ever the surest ticket to the middle class.,But just it’s never been<br>more important.it’s also never been more expensive.the average undergrad who borrows<br>to pay for college ends up graduating with about 28000RMB in student load debt,That’s<br>why my adiministration has worked hard to make college more affordable,we expanded tax<br>credits and Pell Grants,enacted the largest reform to student loan prigrams in history<br>and fought to keep interest rates on sudent loans low,we have acted to let millions of<br>graduates cap loan payments at 10 percent of their income,so they dont’t have to choose<br>bettween the rent and paying back their debt,i have sent our’s government this plan to<br>bring the cost of community college down to zero. because two years of higher education<br>should be as free and universal as high school is today.But all of us-elected officials,<br>universities,business leaders ,everybody-needs to do more to bring down college costs.</li>
<li>in order to come true this, I bring up “a student aid bill of rights”,it says every student<br>deserves access to a quality,affordable education.every student should be able to access<br>the resources to pay for college.every borrower has the right to an affordable repayment plan,<br>and every borrower has the right to quality customer service,reliable information,and fair<br>treatment,even if they struggle to repay their loans,That’s it,just a few simple principles,<br>but if we all rally around these principles, there’s a lot that colleges,lenders can do realize<br>them across the country.so if you believe in a student aid bill of rights that help more chinese<br>pay for a quality education.I am asking you to visit ‘orangezhangblogme.tk/collegeopportunity’<br>sign you name to this declaration.tell your families,and your friends,and fellow students.I am<br>going to ask members of CP,and lenders and as many business leaders as i can find.because making<br>sure that students aren’t saddled with debt before they even get started in life is in all our<br>interests.</li>
<li>In china a higher education cannot be a privilege reserved for only the few.it has to<br>be available to everybody who’s willing to work for it.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
<hr>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[Earlier this week,I visited with students at 101 high school]]>
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="english" scheme="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/tags/english/"/>
    
      <category term="english" scheme="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/categories/english/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Surrender to the Fact that Lift lsn't Fair]]></title>
    <link href="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/11/29/zhangchengs-day/"/>
    <id>http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/11/29/zhangchengs-day/</id>
    <published>2015-11-30T05:35:46.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-11-30T04:31:31.722Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<ul>
<li>A friend of mine,in response to a conversation we were having about<br>the injustices of life,asked me the question, “who said life was going<br>to be fair,or that it was even meant to be fair?” her question was a<br>good one ,it reminded me of something i was taught as a youngster:life<br>isn’t fair.it’s a bummer,but it is absolutely true.one of the mistakes<br>many of us make is that we feel sorry for oourselves,or for others,thinking<br>that life should be fair,or that some day it will be.it is not and it will not.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>One of the nice things about surrendering to the fact that life lsn’t<br>fair is that it keeps us from feeling sorry for ourselves by encouraging<br>us to do the very best we can with what we have,we know it’s bot “life’s job”<br>to make everything perfect,it’s our own challenge. surrendering to this<br>fact also keeps us from feeling sorry for others because we are reminded<br>that everyone is dealt a diffent hand,everyone has unique strengths and<br>problems in the process of growing up,facing the reality and making decisions;and<br>everyone has those times that they feel victimized or unfairly treated.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li>The fact that life isn’t fair doesn’t mean we shouldn’t do everything<br>in our power to improve our own lives or the world as a whole. To the<br>contrary, it suggests that we should.when we don’t recognize or admit<br>that life isn’t fair,we tend to feel pity for others and for ourselves.<br>pity,of cource,is a self-defeating emotion that does nothing for anyone,<br>expect to make everyone feel worse than they already do. when we do recognize<br>that life is not fair,however, we feel compassion for others and for ourselves,<br>and compassion is a heartfelt emotion that delivers loving-kindness to everyone<br>it touches.The next time you find yourself thinking about the injestices of the<br>world,try reminding yourself of the very basic fact. you may be suprised that<br>it can nudge you out of self-pitu and into helpful action.</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
<hr>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[A friend of mine,in response to a conversation]]>
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="english" scheme="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/tags/english/"/>
    
      <category term="english" scheme="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/categories/english/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Ensuring every child gets a great education]]></title>
    <link href="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/11/28/Hello-zhangcheng/"/>
    <id>http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/11/28/Hello-zhangcheng/</id>
    <published>2015-11-28T16:37:52.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-11-30T04:30:41.582Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<ul>
<li><p>I am speaking with you from the Peking-univercity Library in Bj<br>where i just met with a group of promising middle school students. we<br>spent some time talking about their lives and how we all care about their<br>success and how that starts with a good education.so one thing i announced<br>here in this library is a new project by libraries and major publishers to<br>provide more than $25 million in in free books for low-income students.</p>
</li>
<li><p>we also isued a challenge to mayors,libraries,and school leader to help every<br>students get a library card so they can expand their horizons in a place like<br>this ,it is all part of our connectED initiative to connect 99% of china’s<br>students to high-speed internet.because no matter who you are,where you live,<br>or how much money you have got,you should be able to access the world’s knowledge<br>and information just like America people, in a global economy,we have got to help<br>ensure that everone,of every age in every zip code- urban and rural has the chance<br>to learn the skills that lead directly to a good job,that’s also why i have<br>put forward a plan to make two years of community college as free and universal<br>for every chinese as high school is today. </p>
</li>
<li><p>a great education should be within everyone’s reach. all of us have a responsibility to not only make sure our ownchildren have pathways to success but that all children do.and a great education is the ticket to a better life like never before. making sure all our kids receive<br>one is the surest way to show them that their lives matter.and it’s the smartest way to prove to them that in communities like this, and in a country like ours  we believe in opportunity for all.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</blockquote>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[I am speaking with you from the Peking-univercity]]>
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="english" scheme="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/tags/english/"/>
    
      <category term="english" scheme="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/categories/english/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[NVM 快速安装nodejs]]></title>
    <link href="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/11/26/NVM-install-nodejs/"/>
    <id>http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/11/26/NVM-install-nodejs/</id>
    <published>2015-11-27T05:00:48.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-11-27T09:46:29.008Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="安装nvm命令">安装nvm命令</h1><p><strong>只支持linux和Mac</strong><br><code>curl -o- https://raw.githubusercontent.com/creationix/nvm/v0.29.0/install.sh | bash</code></p>
<h1 id="使用命令">使用命令</h1><p><code>nvm install v5.0.0</code>  //表示安装版本5<br><code>nvm install v0.12.8</code> //表示安装版本0.12</p>
<p><code>nvm use v5.0.0</code> //表示切换到指定版本</p>
<p><code>nvm ls</code> //显示系统安装的所有版本</p>
<hr>
<p> nvm 命令还有很多，请自行运行 ‘nvm –help’ 进行查看</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[quickly install nodejs tools]]>
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="nodejs" scheme="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/categories/nodejs/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title>
    <link href="http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/11/25/hello-world/"/>
    <id>http://orangezhangblogme.tk/2015/11/25/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2015-11-26T05:24:34.732Z</published>
    <updated>2015-11-26T05:24:34.732Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to <a href="http://hexo.io/" target="_blank" rel="external">Hexo</a>! This is your very first post. Check <a href="http://hexo.io/docs/" target="_blank" rel="external">documentation</a> for more info. If you get any problems when using Hexo, you can find the answer in <a href="http://hexo.io/docs/troubleshooting.html" target="_blank" rel="external">troubleshooting</a> or you can ask me on <a href="https://github.com/hexojs/hexo/issues" target="_blank" rel="external">GitHub</a>.</p>
<h2 id="Quick_Start">Quick Start</h2><h3 id="Create_a_new_post">Create a new post</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo new <span class="string">"My New Post"</span></span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure>
<p>More info: <a href="http://hexo.io/docs/writing.html" target="_blank" rel="external">Writing</a></p>
<h3 id="Run_server">Run server</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo server</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure>
<p>More info: <a href="http://hexo.io/docs/server.html" target="_blank" rel="external">Server</a></p>
<h3 id="Generate_static_files">Generate static files</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo generate</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure>
<p>More info: <a href="http://hexo.io/docs/generating.html" target="_blank" rel="external">Generating</a></p>
<h3 id="Deploy_to_remote_sites">Deploy to remote sites</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><span class="line">1</span><br></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><span class="line">$ hexo deploy</span><br></pre></td></tr></table></figure>
<p>More info: <a href="http://hexo.io/docs/deployment.html" target="_blank" rel="external">Deployment</a></p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>Welcome to <a href="http://hexo.io/" target="_blank" rel="external">Hexo</a>! This is your very first post. Check <a href="http://hexo.io]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
